

KHANH TRUONG

Frontend Engineer

Location:

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Phone:

0902.340.111

Email:

workhanh79@gmail.com

GitHub:

https://github.com/binnehaha321

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/tqk/

Website:

https://truongquockhanh.info

Summary

I am a Frontend engineer proficient in the Front-end career path who brings a better view to the user through their experience and interaction. I have 2+ years of experience with ReactJS, using JavaScript and Typescript. I'm proficient in building brandy products (I worked on two start-up projects) and handling complex data and the logic of core features.

I am also interested in learning new things, especially to be able to serve the business's needs.

Technical Skills

Programming Languages: JavaScript, Typescript.

Frameworks: ReactJS, NextJS.

Database Management: MySQL, MS SQL Server, MongoDB.

Testing: Postman.

Rest API: Node.JS, Express.JS, Next.JS

Tools: Figma, Sketch, Adobe XD, Slack, Trello.

Version Control System: GitHub.

Libraries: JQuery, Bootstrap, Ant Design,

TailwindCSS, MUI, ChakraUI

Others: Problem solving, Research, Teamwork.

Work Experience

Junior Developer

Feb 2023 - Present

Gira Technology **Responsibility:** Design web flows, UI/UX, and develop Helli, a young start-up product. Scoring, providing comments, and suggesting better phrases are core features. This major is complex in its working flow, with some exceptions because of integrating AI, which causes many unexpected things.

Tech stack: ReactJS, Typescript, RESTful API, Swagger.

Tools: Figma, Trello, Slack, GitHub.

Others: Ant Design, Redux Toolkit, Redux Saga.

Computing Lecturer

Sep 2022 - Present

BTEC FPT British

College

Responsibility: Teaching several foundation subjects for Computer Science students There are such things as Programming (C#), Web development (HTML, CSS, PHP, MySQL), Software development Life Cycle, and cloud computing.

Frontend Lecturer

Sep 2022 - Jun 2023

LIKELION | Responsibility: Training Frontend skills: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Bootstrap 5, ReactJS, RESTful API.

Fresher Developer

Nov 2021 - May 2022

Splus Software **Responsibility:** Converting design from Adobe XD, Figma, and Sketch to HTML, CSS, and JavaScript using Bootstrap for UI components Reporting and fixing bugs daily through estimated progress. Building up with the domains of E-Commerce, Branding Release, and Health Care.

Skills: HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, LESS, JavaScript, JQuery

Projects

Project: Personal portfolio (v2)

Description: A web page summarizes my education and skills. There are awards and achievements in my studying and working processes. They are all rich and valuable experiences, which I carefully put into this so-called personal portfolio.

Role: Frontend Developer

Technologies: Next.js, Typescript, Radix-ui, TailwindCSS

Project: Helli.vn

Description: A platform for practicing IELTS writing, including both grading and giving feedback based on AI. This is an end-to-end product for those planning to earn an IELTS certificate.

Role: Frontend Developer, UX/UI sketching

Technologies: React.js, Typescript, Redux Toolkit, Redux Saga, Ant Design, TailwindCSS

Project: Family Expense

Description: A platform for managing the University of Greenwich Vietnam system, including students, courses, subjects, grades, staff, departments, etc. Moreover, this allows the Student Affair to remove manual interaction with RPA; it automatically uploads a CSV file and handles exceptions.

Role: Frontend Developer, UX/UI sketching

Technologies: React.js, Typescript, Ant Design, Google Spreadsheet API

Project: University of Greenwich system

Description: A platform for managing the University of Greenwich Vietnam system, including students, courses, subjects, grades, staff, departments, etc. Moreover, this allows the Student Affair to remove manual interaction with RPA; it automatically uploads a CSV file and handles exceptions.

Role: Frontend Developer, UX/UI sketching

Technologies: React.js, JavaScript, Redux Toolkit, Ant Design, TailwindCSS

Project: Personal portfolio (v2)

Description: The first portfolio written with HTML5, SCSS, JavaScript, and Bootstrap 5 There are several valuable sections that I omitted in this second version.

Role: Frontend Developer, UX/UI sketching

Technologies: HTML5, SCSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap 5

Education

Computer Science

2019 - 2023

University of **GPA:** 4.0/40.

Greenwich Classification: First honours.

Hobbies

Vietnam

Football

Guitar

Reading

Tennis

Piano

Analysis

Jogging

Composing
Communication